Inherited will,
the tide of the times, people's dreams.
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people seek
the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
Hey, Apis! Who are you talking to?
No! Don't come here!
Didn't Lost Island sink
a long long time ago?
Grandpa Ryu says that
the island will surface again,
but he doesn't seem to remember
clearly where it is and there's no clue.
He was separated from
his friends and lost his energy.
I want to take him back to his home
no matter what it takes.
He always tells me that he'll
get his energy back for sure
once he goes back to the dragons' nest.
So I'll definitely find it for him.
Okay, then! I'll take him
to Lost Island!
Luffy! Were you listening?
Lost Island sank into the sea!
But since the legendary
Millennial Dragon actually exists,
I'm sure Lost Island
also exists somewhere!
An island that's not even on a map?
Yeah, that's why we're going!
"Eric Attacks! Great Escape
from Warship Island!"
It's hot!
What the heck is that?
The marines again?
Hey, everyone! This is so cool!
What's going on here?
And the 1,201st King was…
Geez. The story isn't over yet?
Hey, listen to me.
What? Is it morning already?
I dozed off since the old man's story
was so long.
There's a problem!
Bokuden-san! Where's Apis?
What's the matter?
Ah, you guys are pirates, right?
A marine fleet started blocking
the harbor!
It can't be. Just to capture Apis?
Why are they after a girl like that?
Hey! Everyone, come with me!
Certainly, Nami-san!
Why?
Just do it!
What do we do with the old man?
Looks like he's sound asleep,
so let's let him be.
Hey, when Bokuden-san wakes up,
please tell him that we'll protect Apis.
Okay.
Their ship is on the starboard bow!
Okay! The landing unit will come
to Warship Island with me!
The rest of the crew
is to seize their ship!
Hi, everyone!
This is the Millennial Dragon
Grandpa Bokuden was talking about.
See? Isn't he cool?
Don't talk like he's yours!
When you get closer to the Grand Line,
you run into things like this, huh?
Since there're Sea Kings as well,
I guess this is possible.
Is he really harmless?
Ah! He can be senile sometimes,
so if he acts like you're food, get away!
It's too late!
But it doesn't hurt, right?
I guess you call it soft-mouth?
What are you saying? He's not a puppy.
Let him eat you like that!
Zoro!
Don't! He'll have food poisoning.
What did you say, you damn love cook?
What the marines are after
is this Millennial Dragon.
Frankly, the reason I brought you here
is that we'd like to bring this
Millennial Dragon back to Lost Island.
What are you saying?
The marines are closing in on us!
We're going to have enough
trouble just getting away.
How in the heck could we
take such a big creature--
Grandpa Ryu wants to go home.
So…
Don't tell me, Luffy,
that you promised her, like,
"Yeah! I'll bring him home."
Yeah, I promised and said,
"I'll bring him home."
Don't do that! We don't know
where that island is, right?
How are we supposed to get there?
If we go, it'll work out somehow.
As if!
I thought Grandpa Ryu would get
his energy back once he goes home.
Animals have a migration instinct.
This Millennial Dragon may know something.
Yeah. Let's find Lost Island!
But--
Well, things will probably
work out, don't you think?
Zoro.
That's fine, but what
are we going to do with him?
Just bringing him down the mountain
alone will be a lot of work.
First, build a cart!
A big enough one for Grandpa Ryu to ride.
All right!
Gum-Gum Gatling!
Is this enough?
Yeah. A-okay!
Since you did all this,
I guess I have no choice.
I'll do it. All right, I'll do it!
I guess this is it.
This thing won't break
even when Grandpa Ryu rides it!
Yeah!
But the harbor is blocked
by the marines, right?
What will we do with the ship?
Isn't it going to work out?
No, it won't.
Shall we make a raid?
Yeah, good idea.
That's not going to work
since we have Grandpa Ryu.
I have an idea about how
we can carry him out of here.
By the way, I want the Going Merry
to be brought to the rear of the island.
Okay! It's the precious ship
that Kaya gave us. I'll do it.
He's so cool!
However, Zoro comes with me!
Me too?
Then I'll leave it to you guys.
Okay! So,
how about we wait until nightfall?
No!
Bring the ship to the edge of the cape
that looks like Usopp's nose.
You're right! That's Usopp's nose.
So what are we going to do?
Just bringing the ship won't--
Don't worry about it.
I don't think they'd find
this place so easily,
but in any case, hurry up.
What? Doing things
on a hit-or-miss basis like that isn't--
Sanji-kun! Luffy!
Put Grandpa Ryu on the cart.
-Okay!
-Okay, Nami-san!
Hey, old man!
Where are you hiding this girl?
Hey! Wake up!
Oh. Did I already talk about
the 1,201st King?
What are you talking about?
Lt. Commander!
There are tracks from something
being dragged in the backyard!
Eric! Did you find anything?
These tracks must've been made by them.
They should be hiding
somewhere in the mountain.
Okay! We'll track them down!
This is why I suggested
that we wait until night.
What are you doing?
I'll go on ahead.
Meh mound me!
-It's them!
-Don't let him escape! Fire!
Zoro!
What?
There was another one?
Stop! Stop!
Stop! Or we'll fire!
Stop!
What? Are they going to ram us?
Maht? Mis is mad!
It's going to ram us!
Furl the sails!
It's too late now!
Prepare to set sail!
Yes, sir!
Hoist the anchor!
Furl the sails!
Go after that pirate ship!
-Yes, sir!
Here they come!
We've got trouble!
The bird said that
the marines are getting close!
Oh. They came sooner than I thought.
Hey, what are you going to do now?
You don't have to worry
because we have these two.
Once the Going Merry
is at Usopp's Nose Cape,
we'll go all the way down.
That brat is up there.
What's that?
It's a monster!
I finally found Dragonite,
the elixir of immortality!
Don't panic!
That's the Millennial Dragon
we've been looking for!
We'll get closer to them without being
noticed and capture it in one shot!
-Yes, sir!
Dammit! After we went through
all that trouble to escape!
We haven't yet.
Don't let them get away!
Capture them without fail!
Zoro! Zoro! Zoro! Zoro!
Take care of the sail!
Got it! Leave it to me!
Dammit! Their ship is big but it's fast!
No! Don't shoot Grandpa Ryu!
Apis!
Grandpa Ryu!
As I thought, that brat had something
to do with the Millennial Dragon,
although I didn't think that I'd be able
to encounter a real live dragon.
I no longer care about that brat.
That dragon is the elixir of immortality
that we've been looking for!
Fire!
Stop it!
No use!
What the heck?
The bullets definitely…
So you have powers of a devil fruit.
That's right. I'm a rubber person.
Rubber person!
Devil fruit?
What's that?
-Use--
-Use swords!
Guns don't work against rubber!
Sanji-kun!
Yes, Nami-san!
Gum-Gum Gatling!
You call yourselves the marines?
Really, you guys are good for nothing.
-What was that?
-A knife?
My name is Eric the Whirlwind.
I'm a mercenary hired by Nelson Royal.
We don't have any business
with you pirates.
We have some business
with that Millennial Dragon.
If you stand in my way,
I'll make you a victim of my wind slash,
the power of the Sickle-Sickle Fruit.
-Hey, he said Sicko Sicko.
-Surprised?
-Sicko?
-I have the power…
-What should we do?
-…of a devil fruit, too.
Nami!
Do we have to keep going?
A little bit longer!
Nami-san's lovely even when
she looks at the distant ocean.
Just hurry up.
Hey! You bastards!
Are you listening to me?
You're Eric the Sicko, right?
We're listening.
That's not right!
I didn't say sicko, I said sickle,
like the one that slices!
We're sicko talking about this!
Just kidding!
Hope you don't regret making me angry.
Sickle-Sickle…
Whirlwind!
What was that?
I see. A wind slash, huh?
The winds I create are as sharp
as legendary swords.
No matter how trained you are,
it's easy for me to tear you apart.
Aren't we going yet?
No. Not yet!
Now, out of my way!
Hand over the Millennial Dragon!
No way!
Do you wanna experience
the Sickle-Sickle Whirlwind again?
Aren't we going yet, Nami-san?
Here they come! They're here!
Now! Sanji-kun! Luffy!
Okay, Nami-swan!
-What?
-We'll be right there!
Nami-san! I'll be your love catapult!
I won't let you escape!
Gum-Gum…
Sickle-Sickle…
Pistol!
Whirlwind!
I won't let you escape.
We're going to run into a rock!
Luffy!
Gum-Gum Gatling!
What is this?
That's how I do it.
Dumbass!
That was close.
Yahoo!
Nami said to come to
the edge of that cape, right?
Yeah.
Darn. We couldn't get rid of them.
Well, after all, we have no choice
but to make a raid. Yikes!
Go! Go!
Go!
Yahoo!
What a crazy plan that was!
Well, it worked out!
Exactly.
Go after them! Go after that ship!
We can't move because
the sail is in our way!
What?
I think this will do.
That was fun.
That was fun!
Apis! Are you okay?
Yep!
Luffy, we can leave any time now.
Okay!
Set sail for Lost Island!
But which way?
That way? Or maybe this way?
Huh? Huh? Huh?
Are we going to be okay
when you're so unreliable?
Well, we'll just have to go.
It's not on the sea chart, either, so…
You're lovely, Nami-san,
even when you're decisive.
You know…
Our destination is Lost Island!
-Which direction is Lost Island?
-Who knows.
Grandpa Ryu is sleeping, so…
You're so irresponsible…
I don't see it on the sea chart.
A ship has appeared right in front of us!
That's the Going Merry!
Hey, could this place be…
Is this the legendary island?
On the next episode of ONE PIECE!
"A Solitary Island in the Distant Sea!
The Legendary Lost Island."
I'm going to be King of the Pirates!